{
    "subject": "resource/WGGS-TV",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/North_Carolina",
    "human_readable": "WGGS-TV is located in North Carolina.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9698317050933838,
            "question": "Can you name a city in North Carolina that might be near WGGS-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8822169303894043,
            "question": "Where is WGGS-TV located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6025646328926086,
            "question": "In which US region would you find WGGS-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5830367803573608,
            "question": "What state is home to WGGS-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5075392723083496,
            "question": "Does WGGS-TV broadcast locally or nationally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4875700771808624,
            "question": "Who are the owners of WGGS-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4854484796524048,
            "question": "What type of station is WGGS-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4264311194419861,
            "question": "How might the location of WGGS-TV influence its programming?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29588547348976135,
            "question": "Does WGGS-TV have a website or social media presence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23675979673862457,
            "question": "What programming does WGGS-TV offer?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=WGGS-TV is located in North Carolina.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6105_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does WGGS-TV have a website or social media presence?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6105_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might the location of WGGS-TV influence its programming?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6105_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of station is WGGS-TV?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6105_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6105_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6105_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6105_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6105_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6105_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6105_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6105_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6105_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6105_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6105_59.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents state that WGGS-TV serves audiences in northern South Carolina and western North Carolina, it specifically mentions being **located in Greenville, South Carolina.**  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to the provided context information, WGGS-TV is explicitly stated to be located in Greenville, South Carolina, not North Carolina."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that WGGS TV 16 is located in Greenville, South Carolina. There is no information supporting its location in North Carolina."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "WGGS-TV is located in Greenville, South Carolina.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}